

TRINH PHAM

DIGITAL EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

PROFILE

Trinh Pham is a multidisciplinary designer who focuses on the methodology and principles of both UX/UI design and motion graphics animation.

With her ability to explore and "consume" new creative solutions and technology, she is able to combine her compassion and love for design and illustrations to create the best experience for her users.

EXPERIENCES

Freelance Designer | MAY 2017 - PRESENT

Working as a contracter doing various design work (mostly ux/ui, branding and motion) for different clients and companies.

Internship at Forge Media + Design | MAY 2018 - SEPT 2018

I joined the Interactive Team as a UX/UI + motion graphic designer. I was responsible for helping out with any graphic design, building mockups/ prototypes, production, execution as needed.

Internship at Metub Network | JULY 2017 - AUGUST 2017

Worked at Metub Network (a leading Digital entertainment company) in Vietnam as a Motion Graphic Designer. Ability to work with variety projects with the main production and design team of the company.

UX Researcher For Sunlife Financial | AUG 2017 - DEC 2017

We did multiple user usability testings and analyzed datas to help enhance the user experience on the Sunlife website.

SSU Safe Walk | AUGUST 2017 - 2019

Ability to safely escort students and staff accross campus. Being a staff in Sheridan Studen Union Group, I have contribute in school's activities to create a safe environment and better experience for students.

Child & Youth Work at Chau Ro | APRIL 2014

Working as a volunteer. Helping kids to fully express their artistic abilities and teaching Vietnamese as a second language



Oakville, Ontario



+1 6479077545



trinhboni@gmail.com

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2015 GOVERNOR SIMCOE HIGH SCHOOL [Graduated with Honors]

BACHELOR OF INTERACTION DESIGN

SEPTEMBER 2015 - 2019 SHERIDAN COLLEGE

SKILLS

After Effects CINEMA 4D

UX / UI Design Sketch

HTML / CSS Adobe Suite

PORTFOLIO



trinhphamdesign.com

SOCIAL

(i) /trinhphamdesign/

in /trinh-pham-aa5959135

